[Unsoiled Starlight]
[Episode 20]
[Adapted from Migu's novel
"Unsoiled Starlight"]
[Original Author: Shan Gu Jun]
Congratulations on your wedding!
It's delicious!
Let's eat.
Here.
By the way, Tinglan,
is your law firm busy lately?
I have a case from a financial company
and want to cooperate with you.
Director Xiao needs
to review the case first.
Well,
you send me the documents,
I'll sort them out
and pass them to her tomorrow.
That's great!
This financial project is...
Are we going to eat or what?
"Are we going to eat or what? "
I forgot.
Your better half
doesn't talk about work after hours.
You should
keep a closer eye on him from now on.
He's so inefficient.
Shut your mouth.
What's wrong?
Are you in a bad mood today?
No,
just a little tired.
Just eat.
Shushu,
you went to the hospital
for a follow-up checkup today.
What did the doctor say?
The doctor said it's fine,
and I'm recovering well.
What is it?
So mysterious
that we have to talk here.
I remember your dad used to work
in database-related jobs, right?
Yes,
what's wrong?
I want to ask your dad to help me
introduce an expert in this field.
Oh,
preferably someone
who doesn't have deep ties
with commercial companies.
What happened?
Is it
related to Zhuo Yu'an?
Not exactly,
but this matter
must be kept from him.
I can't explain it
clearly to you right now.
Can you help me?
Don't worry,
If you need me,
I will definitely be there.
Alright,
leave it to me.
[Data error]
Why did you come back early today?
Is there something wrong?
Oh,
I plan to bring my mom home to live
next weekend,
so I want to come over
and clean up first.
Oh.
This door lock,
why isn't my code working?
Since you are away from home before,
so I turned it off
for you.
I saw it said some system error.
It's been updating recently.
I'll register a new one for you later.
By the way,
I got a new sofa for you.
See if you like it.
Yes, Nannan.
I found the person for you.
He does academic research
at the institute,
and has absolutely no interest
in the deception of the business world.
Your will meet him this afternoon
at the cafe opposite your company.
Okay.
I got it.
That's roughly my situation.
So I wanted to ask
if it's possible
to find similar data in the system.
The cyber world
is just like the real world.
As long as it existed,
it will leave traces.
Recovering a system account
is a very simple operation.
But to access the backend database,
only internal company personnel can do it.
External intrusion is illegal.
I understand that.
So I wanted to ask Mr. He,
could there be
any other way?
Coincidentally,
our institution
is currently researching
issues related to user privacy.
I can try to get
the official data
as a research case.
But apart from your points of suspicion,
I can't disclose other data.
Understood.
Thank you very much.
I will also keep it strictly confidential.
You're welcome.
Work call.
You go in first.
Hello.
Mr. He.
I found the operation trajectory.
There really is a hypnotic code.
Really?
Even luckier,
the developer of the program and I
worked together a while ago.
He confirmed
that it was commissioned by
a foreign researcher.
But that person only promised
to use it for
internal testing.
I don't know how it got used
in your system.
The name of the commissioner,
is it convenient for you to tell me?
It's Jane.
Mom.
What?
Zhuo told me about your marriage.
Mom, these are tears of joy.
As for being discharged,
I don't want to add to your burden.
I'll just stay in the hospital.
If you have time in the future,
just come and see me,
and I'll be satisfied.
Mom.
You don't need to worry about that.
Tinglan's business is my business.
I will always put Tinglan first.
Then what if one day,
it's Zhuoyuan Technology and me?
Lanlan.
Throwing a childish temper again.
You two,
must live a good life together.
Tolerate each other,
and learn to give in.
Zhuo Yu'an.
After packing up in a couple of days,
I want to move back home.
It's okay if
that house is empty for a while.
Besides,
since the company is closer to you,
isn't it more convenient?
I just feel like
you don't really want me to move back.
Not at all.
Did you know
there was something wrong with that house?
I knew it.
Then since you knew,
why didn't you tell me?
The company is already conducting
an internal investigation.
The process is ongoing.
As for Wen Jian,
I won't let her participate
in the development
of any core content anymore.
I've already arranged for her
to go abroad.
From beginning to end,
when did I ever mention Wen Jian?
So you knew all along
the reason for my illness,
and you even knew who was behind it.
You didn't tell me immediately.
You're even covering up for her.
I'm not covering up for Wen Jian.
I need time.
I need a suitable opportunity
to handle this matter.
She is your partner.
But do you even know
what Wen Jian and I are to each other?
She is Shu Minghai's
illegitimate daughter.
Shu Minghai,
who is my father in name,
had the nerve to
to make her my neighbor.
We grew up together.
Under the guise
that their family had no man,
he asked my mom to take good care of them.
Growing up,
in everything,
he always taught me
to go easy on Wen Jian.
But what was the result?
After he died,
he left all his property to them.
My mom and I
only got a useless corpse
and his debts.
Even
my mom becoming like this
is also their fault.
After what happened last time,
I originally thought
everything could be brushed off.
We could live our lives
without interfering with each other.
She actually went even further
and wanted my life.
Zhuo Yu'an,
where exactly do you put
me and my interests?
Shu Tinglan,
you and I always share the same interests.
You have to believe me on this.
But between Wen Jian and me,
there is a company to maintain.
I need to figure out a proper way
to completely resolve this matter.
That's exactly your way
of doing things, Zhuo Yu'an.
But as the person involved,
and even more as the victim,
I can't weigh the pros and cons
like you do.
Since you can't solve it,
then whatever I do from now on,
I don't need your approval
or your opinion.
If you don't agree with my approach,
let's dissolve our marriage.
Shu Tinglan.
This is too much.
How could he do this?
Shushu.
Let's put aside
what Zhuo Yu'an did now.
The most important thing is this Wen Jian.
If you go easy on her this time,
she will definitely be
even more brazen next time.
Got it.
I don't plan to go easy on her.
It's just...
You just don't want
to implicate Zhuo Yu'an.
Thinking about it,
it's all Zhuo Yu'an's fault.
Why did he have to partner with Wen Jian?
In that case,
we might as well blame Shu Minghai.
He's been dead for so long.
One person's mistake
makes so many people pay for it.
Nannan.
About this matter,
I didn't want to drag you into it.
But if I want to use
online public opinion and trends,
I can only rely on you.
Don't worry.
When have I ever
have I ever let you down?
Alright, leave it to me.
Leave it to me.
Knockout with one punch.
Alright, alright.
Just leave it to me.
Alright, don't worry.